{
    "subject": "resource/Paul_Verdzekov",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1931-01-22",
    "human_readable": "Paul Verdzekov was born on January 22, 1931.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9416747093200684,
            "question": "Is Paul Verdzekov's birth date in January?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9164242148399353,
            "question": "When was Paul Verdzekov born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8443994522094727,
            "question": "What month was Paul Verdzekov born in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8228215575218201,
            "question": "What is Paul Verdzekov's birth date?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8010461330413818,
            "question": "What day of the month was Paul Verdzekov born on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6167510151863098,
            "question": "How old is Paul Verdzekov now?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5289917588233948,
            "question": "In what year did Paul Verdzekov come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5242592692375183,
            "question": "Calculate Paul Verdzekov's age."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.460784912109375,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Paul Verdzekov's life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3812063932418823,
            "question": "Is January 22nd a common birthdate?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Paul Verdzekov was born on January 22, 1931.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2278_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Paul Verdzekov's life?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2278_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Calculate Paul Verdzekov's age.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2278_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=In what year did Paul Verdzekov come into the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2278_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2278_10.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2278_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2278_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2278_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2278_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2278_36.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2278_38.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2278_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2278_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2278_46.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information provided clearly states that Paul Verdzekov was born on January 22, 1931, in the document \"file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_2278/re-ranker-msmarco/16.txt\"."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}